NATSUKIYA
RAMEN
Why?
Why not go with your usual
clear-broth shoyu ramen!
Why do you want the rich seafood
and tonkotsu thick broth tsukemen?
A soldier's thirst
can't be quenched with this!
Ya idiot!
Tsukemen has always been
the thing for the front line!
Why...
Seafood and tonkotsu...
Their throats...
THE IMPOSSIBLE AFTERMATH
OF AN IMPOSSIBLE GAME / SATURDAY, JUNE 6th
I'm begging you, Noren!
Don't wake up quite yet!
Noren Mitsuoka is already hypnotized.
When she wakes, she will fall in love
with the first person she sees!
The hell?
Eiji Rindou's a given,
but don't look at Tenma, either!
If you look...
MINCEMEAT / LOVE / LOVE / LOVE
PRETENDING TO DATE
...the relationship chart
will get way too confusing!
Things will get awkward
in the home ec club!
CHASHU TOPPING
Huh?
Why are you filling the barrels
with chashu pork?
This is for peace!
I can't fire that anymore!
Are you sure?
I think you can fire if you tried!
Hm?
Powdered fish?
Huh?
Oh...
You're right.
Stop it!
Powdered fish...
makes customers thirsty.
Time out!
Let's catch our breaths!
Sorry for tossing this to you!
I bought these before coming here.
Anyway, this guy's incredible!
I've never golfed before,
but he seems really good at it!
That kind of accuracy and power
isn't something you can learn in a day.
He should try becoming a pro golfer!
I don't really know this guy's deal...
but he's the type who can choose
whether or not he kills someone.
It sucks, considering
he's got all that skill...
and I don't want to fight him
when I'm feeling like this.
MY NOTE BOOK
CRAYONS
AGREED
"Agreed"...
Wait, you can give a piece of your mind!
YOU'RE AMAZING. DON'T WANNA KILL YOU.
"You're amazing. Don't wanna kill you."
Wha...
Then let's stop all this crap!
BUT I CAN'T DITCH MY MISSION.
"But I can't ditch my mission."
"And can't think hard now."
AND CAN'T THINK HARD NOW.
MY BROTHER IS TRYING TO FIX THAT.
"My brother is trying to fix that."
I WANNA FIX, TOO.
"I wanna fix, too."
"Want it to end for him."
"He's a bit scary..."
"HE'S A BIT SCARY, BUT MY BROTHER
IS THE MOST IMPORTANT TO ME."
"...but my brother
is the most important to me."
You got me there!
I can't pull back!
And I'm not a good negotiator!
I really shouldn't learn about
the opponent before my match.
That doesn't mean...
it's okay for me to lose, though!
Well...
Let's get back to the game!
Tenma!
Are you okay?
Ogami! What about you?
Yeah! I'm done on my end!
Huh?
What about Noren?
Good! She's not awake yet!
You're done? That means...
Yeah!
I took out the older brother.
Boss, that's the worst way to put it!
You haven't killed him!
Oh, sorry. Old habits.
Ogami! Don't tell me you...
fought the other one and killed—
Did not!
I just knocked his lights out!
But I think that guy thinks
you killed his big bro!
He snapped and started shooting everywhere!
That makes the balls harder to dodge
and impossible to shoot down!
Shit, how am I gonna stop this?
A few shots into his limbs?
No, a headshot?
In either case,
I can't let Tenma see blood!
Ogami! Let me take over!
Huh?
Get his attention...
even for just a few seconds!
And I'll show you a real killer shot!
Hey, over here!
Drive that ball at me!
Boss?
No problem!
A killer shot? For real?
But Tenma ain't the type to call bluffs.
If you're saying you can do it...
I believe you.
Soccer's another type of game
where you can put spin on the ball.
For example, there are banana kicks
and knuckleball shots.
But there is one type of spin
you almost never see in soccer.
You know what that is?
No clue. Never thought about it.
A spiral!
In other words, a gyro spin!
It's just like a bullet.
Making the ball spiral around
the direction it's traveling
really ups it penetration potential.
At least on paper.
You just came up with that
while fooling around, right?
Quit acting like you're smart.
For real?
You cracked concrete!
How's that?
It's powerful, but it leaves me wide open.
So, I can't use it during a game.
That's useless.
Sorry man, but I'm putting an end to this!
Super Gyro Spin Shot!
Damn, seriously?
He just took out a JARDIN hitman!
We somehow got through it,
but this mess...
What the hell are we gonna do?
Ogami!
I have so much I wanna ask you!
You know what's up
with these guys, don't you?
Well, um...
Boss...
We can't clean up this mess!
We're totally screwed!
- Huh?
Morning.
Huh?
Ogami?
Oh...
U-Um...
What the...
Why was I asleep here of all places?
That's right!
I was suddenly assaulted
by two guys in the movie theater.
Don't tell me...
You saved me again.
Nope.
It wasn't me.
I'm so happy! Thank you!
I helped, too.
"Again"?
Damn, this girl might be catching on
that he saved her in the past!
This keeps getting worse
on so many levels!
Oh, I'm sorry!
I was so happy I couldn't help it!
Nope.
Boss, have you been trembling
for the past few minutes?
O-Of course I am!
I told you Noren is the same age
as my daughter!
That's enough of a reason
to not be okay with this!
I mean, if it was a five-year-old...
Papa, I love you!
I wanna marry you!
I'm so happy! I love you, too!
...now that'd be okay!
That's totally heartwarming!
I'm sure that's a good daddy
who really loves his kid! Good for him!
But when they get to a sensible age,
and say the same thing
in a serious voice...
I really do want to marry you, Papa!
You're kidding me?
I'm serious!
Why?
Now that would send shivers
down any normal dad's spine!
Any guy who's into that goes
to a special place in Hell after he dies!
Well, probably!
B-B-Boss...
A hitman is talking about Hell?
In either case, we...
I don't need a grim remark like that!
I know all too well!
Ogami...
Maybe this is like
the suspension bridge effect.
I don't get it...
but my heart's been racing
for a while now!
This might not be
something I should say now...
but maybe...
Just maybe...
Ogami, I might be...
f-falling in—
- Huh?
What?
What the hell are you doing, Ogami?
Even from my perspective,
you guys had something going!
What's with the karate chop to the neck?
Oh, there was a mosquito.
You slap mosquitos!
You don't karate chop them!
Is it really okay to save the heroine
and then knock her out?
I was so confident in my
brother's victory heading over.
I never thought it would end up this way.
Kazuma Rindou! What the hell...
Hold on a sec, Ogami!
Huh?
Something's weird about him!
Why's he wearing Chisato's clothes?
Oh, no. These aren't hers.
I bought the same outfit.
Wait, hold up!
We'll talk about that later.
Calm down, Tenma.
Well, indeed.
Now that it's come to this,
there's only one thing to do.
Plead for my life.
- Huh?
I beg of you. I'll be fine.
I'll do anything.
So, please, Eiji's life if nothing else.
Can you spare him?
In our world,
failure or defeat means death.
I've resolved to accept my fate,
but even so...
I wanna fight
for my brother's life to the end!
Please!
Well, um... I didn't intend
to do that to begin with.
Huh? Are you asking Ogami?
I didn't, either!
I'm not thinking of taking time
to deliver a killing blow after all this!
And there ya have it.
We gotta talk, so I can't tell you
to go home just yet.
But when it's over, you can
take him away wherever you want.
I see.
Apologies.
You have my gratitude.
Now, I said "when it's over."
It's far from over.
This place is a huge mess.
I think I'm about to cry.
What do we do now?
Wait. Hold on just a minute!
Before we do anything,
there's something I gotta ask.
Who the hell are you guys?
I was thinking while we were fighting
that you guys aren't normal.
At first, you seemed like
bad guys out to kidnap Noren.
But you guys are on a different level
from thugs or the yakuza.
Ogami, you seem to know a bit
of what's going on, too.
Just maybe...
You're from the same world as these guys?
Boss!
Maybe Kazuma might...
Right!
Hey, can you make him forget everything
about today with your hypnosis?
Huh? I can do that, but...
Please, just do it!
I will count to three.
When I finish counting and
you hear the lighter close,
you will instantly fall asleep.
When you wake up, you'll have
forgetten everything about today.
Three...
two...
one.
What the hell was that
just now? Cut it out!
Huh? It's not working?
What?
O-One more time!
Hey.
Once more!
I told you!
This guy...
Impossible!
My hypnosis... isn't working!
Huh?
What's going on here?
You were saying
you were good, cheap, and fast!
I never said I was like a beef bowl chain!
I said "anyone...
powerfully and instantly"!
But this is a first for me!
What is up with this guy?
He is way too extraordinary!
B-Boss...
At this point...
I just gotta laugh.
That's the way Tenma is.
I gotta say the jig is up for real now.
Hitmen?
Guys like that really exist?
B-Boss, was it really okay to tell him?
It ain't good.
I can't go to school anymore.
The mission is over,
and I'm unemployed starting tomorrow.
It's all over as of today.
Sorry for trying to hypnotize you earlier.
And you have my thanks
for helping me save Noren.
Ogami, you're going to go away, too?
Yeah.
Huh?
It's bad for a hitman to come to school?
- Huh?
I mean, killing people
is something you should never do.
More like, stop doing that right now.
But isn't that all the more reason
for you to go to school?
So you can find a different career path?
You were going because
you had to for work, right?
At least, that's
what it looked like to me.
I know that you quitting now won't make
everything you did in the past okay.
BUT I CAN'T DITCH MY MISSION.
AND CAN'T THINK HARD NOW.
MY BROTHER IS TRYING TO FIX THAT.
But in the end...
I don't think you guys are all that bad.
I mean, you like school
and studying, right?
Then don't give up on that.
You can change, look ahead,
and come to school again.
I won't blow your cover or anything.
What's with them?
First Master, then Big Sis...
and this guy, too?
I can't tell who's the adult
and who's the kid.
No.
Maybe stuff like that
doesn't matter at all.
I've been taught so much
ever since I started going to school.
And that goes for you brothers, too!
You can't kill! Ever!
Oh, you're right.
What you're saying... is something
my brother might also say.
- Huh?
- Oh!
Sirens?
Hey, Kazuma!
No, this isn't one of my tricks.
It's a real report.
You guys go out the back.
Huh?
I have hypnosis.
Coming up with a story
to cover my ass is easy for me.
I was already planning
on doing that anyway.
But...
You might fail.
Tenma is an exception!
No, we're not done quite yet!
Undo the hypnosis you put on Noren!
Sorry, got no time for that!
I'll take care of that next time!
Huh?
I've already put in
the paperwork...
so I'll be seeing you again soon enough.
There's no doubt that the girl
is a clue for me to cure my brother.
I'll forego the duel for now...
but in the near future...
we'll be transferring to your school.
Really? I'm counting on that!
It better be sooner
than just the near future, too!
Are you all right?
Are you hurt?
Are you okay, too?
Are you hurt—
MODERN MIDDLE SCHOOL
MATH 1
Man, that was one hellish weekend!
Tell me about it.
It's great that you can go back
to school again!
One way or another.
In the end, even putting my age aside,
Tenma caught on to my job.
And it's entirely likely that hitmen
targeting Noren will drop by again.
We really need to rethink
a lot of stuff here.
Besides...
This case ain't over yet.
Sounds like the Rindou brothers will be
transferring to this middle school, too.
Ogami...
But until then,
Noren is still under hypnosis.
On top of it, the spell puts her
into 100% serious love mode,
so she's strangely assertive!
Starting today, I can't drop my guard
at school even for an instant.
Why don't you just stay home?
No way. I wanna study.
Whatever happens,
I have to do everything in my power...
to avoid even accidentally advancing
my relationship with Noren!